x197142-BASEPLAN
x197142-ELEC EQUIP
VA Mechanical 197142-20942-BA S:\clients/197-RSI Group 197-142-DHC, Midlothian Depot,  VA Mechanical 197142-M2.0.dwg DATE: Sep 23, 2025 12:02pm
XREFS: 197142-TBLK-M x197142-RCP PLAN
8
12-6
120
18"
129 140
12"
10-012
22 X14
12
+48
14"0
18-5"
+48"
14"
714.966.9400 WWW. rsi-group.com
SANYA PHATCHARAKITI, License #0402065627 Expiration Date: 09/30/2026 ENGINEERING CO GROUP, INC. Mechanical | Electrical | Plumbing 17151 NEWHOPE STREET, SUITE 108 FOUNTAIN VALLEY, CALIFORNIA 92708 PHONE: 714-847-7100 WWW.CROEG.COM
1. ALL GREASE EXHAUST DUCTWORK SHALL BE DOUBLE-WALL FACTORY BUILT GREASE DUCT FOR USE WITH TYPE I KITCHEN HOOD THAT CONFORMS TO THE REQUIREMENTS OF NFPA-96. PRODUCT SHALL BEETL BE ETL LISTED TO UL-1978 & UL-2221. 2. ANY CHANGES MADE TO THE DESIGN IDENTIFIED ON THESE DRAWINGS AND/OR ASSOCIATED SPECIFICATIONS SHALL BE SUBMITTED TO THE ENGINEER/ARCHITECT OF RECORD FOR REVIEW AND APPROVAL PRIOR TO MAKING ANY MODIFICATIONS TO THE PROJECT. ANY LIABILITY AS A RESULT OF DESIGN MODIFICATIONS, AS WELL AS ANY COST ASSOCIATED WITH SUCH MODIFICATIONS, MADE WITHOUT THE WRITTEN APPROVAL OF THE ENGINEER/ARCHITECT OF RECORD SHALL BECOME THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE CONTRACTOR. 3. PROVIDE MANUAL VOLUME DAMPERS AT ALL BRANCH DUCTS. PROVIDE CABLE/ ELECTRONIC VOLUME DAMPERS AT ALL IN-ACCESSABLE CEILING LOCATIONS,
8. CONTRACTOR TO PROVIDE NECESSARY CONTROL DEVICES TO ENSURE THE SYSTEM FUNCTIONS PROPERLY.
12. PROVIDE CLEAR THERMOSTAT LOCKABLE BOX.
118 STAINLESS STEEL DOUBLE WALL FACTORY BUILT GREASE DUCT INTO HOOD (2,800 CFM 1,584 FPM)
2 STAINLESS STEEL DOUBLE-WALL FACTORY BUILT GREASE DUCT. THE SLOPE OF THE HORIZONTAL DUCT SHALL NOT BE LESS THAN THE MANUFACTURER'S INSTALLATION INSTRUCTION (SLOPE SHALL BE 1/16" PER LINEAR FOOT FOR HORIZONTAL DUCT RUN LESS THAN 75', AND 3/16" PER LINEAR FOOT FOR HORIZONTAL DUCT RUN MORE THAN 75: PER CAPTIVEAIRE DOUBLE WALL GREASE EXHAUST AIR DUCT INSTALLATION INSTRUCTION) TOWARD THE HOOD OR TOWARD THE APPROVED GREASE RESERVOIR. 3 CLEAN-OUT ACCESS DOORS AT EVERY 12-0" O.C. AND AT EACH CHANGE OF DIRECTION FOR ALL HORIZONTAL GREASE DUCT. 4 180 STAINLESS STEEL DOUBLE WALL FACTORY BUILT GREASE DUCT UP TO ROOF (2,800 CFM 1,584 FPM) SEE M3.0 FOR CONTINUATION.
6 SUPPLY AND RETURN AIR DUCT AND UP TO DOAS-1 SEE M3.0 FOR CONTINUATION. 7 4 RESTROOM EXHAUST AIR DUCT UP TO ROOF TERMINATE WITH FACTORY ROOF CAP (80 CFM) - SEE M3.0 FOR CONTINUATION. 8 NO DUCTS AND PIPING TO RUN ABOVE ELECTRICAL PANELS AND TRANSFORMERS PER NEC REQUIREMENTS, SEE CONSTRICTION NOTE #42 ON M1.0. 9 PROVIDE REMOTE TEST INDICATORS (RTI) FOR SMOKE DETECTOR NEXT TO ITS THERMOSTAT. LABEL
10 THERMOSTAT SHALL BE HONEYWELL T10+. THERMOSTAT SHALL BE PRE-SET AT 72░F AND THE AC SHALL OPERATE FROM 10AM TO 12AM. PROVIDE WITH CLEAR PLASTIC THERMOSTAT COVER.
